yourpersonalbrandname.com 2018-08-20

# Privacy Policy for Your Personal Brand Name

## Who we are

Our website address is: [http://yourpersonalbrandname.com](http://yourpersonalbrandname.com/)

What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

This website uses a WordPress plugin for its contact form. If you submit an inquiry through the contact form, we will be sent your name, email address, contact number and any comments you provide. This is so that we know how to contact you to reply to you. The information submitted through the contact form is not retained or used for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

### Analytics - Statcounter

Our website uses Statcounter to monitor website traffic to our site. Statcounter is an anonymous web tracking service who don't attempt to identify an individual person . Their focus is on what visitors to the website do and not on who the visitors are. No personal visitor data is stored.

### Ads

We use [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense) to display ads that help support our website. Please see [Google Adsense Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

We will only store your name, contact email address and phone number if you are a client and have opted to receive promotional emails from us. Please click the unsubscribe link in the footer of the email if you no longer wish to receive marketing material from us. Please contact us if you would like this information deleted from our secure server.

Additionally if you place an order on our online shop in addition to the above information we will retain your address in order to deliver your order. In compliance with the GDPR “right to be forgotten” please contact us if you would like any personal data deleted. See how to contact us below.

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

Our website has a SSL certificate. An SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) certificate is a digital certificate that authenticates the identity of a website and encrypts information sent to the server.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

In the event of a breach, anyone for whom we have an email address will be notified immediately. We also notify known authorities of any breach that puts your personal data in jeopardy.

### What third parties we receive data from

We do not receive personally identifying information from third-parties at this time.

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

We do not use automated decision-making or profiling tools that require user data.

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

This is a private information Website, a “blog”, and as such it is not subject to any industry regulatory requirements (to the best of our knowledge).

## How to contact us

You can send us any questions, concerns, or requests regarding your personal data through our website please send your question on an email to [mike@intelligentweb.co.za](mailto:mike@intelligentweb.co.za)
